Amanda Steele Show.
Things I Learned This Week, yeah.
This Things I Learned This Week is about some fairly recent milestones in women's history
that I consider to be very shocking.
It wasn't until 1976 in Ireland that women were allowed to own their homes.
1976?
Yes.
It wasn't until 1987 in Austria that girls were allowed to take geometry in school.
It wasn't until 1991 that it became illegal in the UK to rape your wife.
91, 1991, 1991.
Last but not least, 2006, for the first time in history,
an accurate description of the clitoris is included in anatomy teaching shows and, like, schools.
Oh, six.
What country was this?
America.
Wow.
And to my knowledge, women in America could not have checking accounts without their husband
until, like, 1975.
Something crazy like that.
So just something to keep in mind.
When we act like, you know, these things happened so long ago and we've made it so far,
they could turn back time.
I'll bet they would find a way.
If they could.
All right.
We up, we up, we up.